# Minh Tran

## Software Engineer Intern

I'm a self-taught software engineer with a strong passion for building efficient and user-centered applications. Over the past 8 years, I have worked in the advertising industry, creating numerous websites and applications.

Through hands-on projects, online coursework (foundation in JavaScript, Python, NodeJS), and consistent problem-solving (via platforms like LeetCode, GitHub, etc.)

Now, I want to dive deeper into development and improve my skills independently. I am seeking an opportunity to learn more and collaborate with a development team where I can continue to grow and contribute meaningful impact.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

# Software Developer PECA - My own product

Nov 2024 - Present

- Assisted in developing a CRM software upgrade that saved an annual budget of \$80K, improving customer service by 73%
- Streamlined 17 existing applications for a more intuitive workflow; reduced interface complexity by 92%
- Collaborated with a 5-member team to release a new system suite; saving the company \$21K in monthly QA costs
- Partnered with 11 supervisors to develop tools that reduced debugging time 72%, saving engineers from repeatitive tasks.

# Advertising Industry Apr 2018 - Present Mirum, Dentsu, Hakuhodo Vietnam

- Serval Web design for advertising campaign (short-term and long-term).
- Familiar with design tools set (Figma, Framer Adobe XD, etc,.) and UX/UI design skill.
- Work with develop team directly (Frontend) to built Microsite, Mobile Web App and Internal Work Management Application.

#### CONTACT

- Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam
- +84 965.353.625
- tgminh1995@gmail.com
- linkedin.com/in/akira-minhtran15
- github.com/FLATBOY

#### **SKILLS**

#### Tech Skills:

- Debugging
- Coding
- · Web Programming
- · Software design and testing
- Web Development

#### Industry Knowledge:

- Software Development
- Visual Design (UX/UI)
- Amazon Web Services
- · Object Oriented Programing
- System Pattern

#### Tools and Software:

- React, Python, NodeJS, ExpressJS
- Swift
- MongoDB, PostgreSQL
- · Basic Linux, Docker
- Figma, Adobe XD, Framer

### **EDUCATION**

Self-taught 2019-Present
MindX Technology 2023-2024
School
Harvard CS50 2021-2022

2020-2021

### **OTHER**

freeCodeCamp

MindX Full stack Certificate